<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Yilong Zhang | 张亦龙</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Yilong Zhang | 张亦龙</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/books/</guid>
      <description>  R for Clinical Study Reports and Submission (2021, work in progress) Slides for a workshop | Slides for a talk  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colophon</title>
      <link>/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/colophon/</guid>
      <description> Typography  Source Sans 3 DM Serif Text IBM Plex Mono Tailwind CSS Typography  Publishing  Site generator: blogdown, driven by Hugo Theme: hugo-nanx2023, built on Bootstrap 5 Commenting: utterances  Editing  R Markdown: RStudio Desktop HTML, CSS, JavaScript: Visual Studio Code  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/papers/</guid>
      <description>Profiles  Google Scholar: full list of publications. ORCID   Selected publications   SMIM: A unified framework of survival sensitivity analysis using multiple imputation and martingale.
Yang, Shu, Yilong Zhang, Guanghan Frank Liu, and Qian Guan. Biometrics (2021+)
  Analysis and reporting in regulated clinical trial environment using R.
Peikun Wu, Palukuru Uday Preetham, Luo Yiwen, Nepal Sarad, Yilong Zhang. PharmaSUG (2021)
  A numerical strategy to evaluate performance of predictive scores via a copula‐based approach</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/</guid>
      <description>R packages Reporting  r2rtf
Easily create production-ready Rich Text Format (RTF) tables and figures
CRAN | GitHub  Infrastructure and automation  pkglite
Compact package representations
CRAN | GitHub  Statistical methods   gsdmvn
Group sequential design for non-proportional hazards
GitHub
  smim
Survival sensitivity analysis using multiple imputation and martingale
GitHub | Paper
  simuCCP
Simulating time to event data with pre-defined predictive metrics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description> 2021  R for Clinical Study Reports and Submission
R/Pharma Conference (workshop)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
